was so tragic that
it deeply affected
our team. I mean
that day was like,
I'd just seen him
cute freckles and
it's like funny, 😂
happy disposition
and it was gone.
And for sure my
mind 🤯 could not wrap
itself around that.
I still cannot
believe he's gone.
Little Eli had just
returned home 🏠 from
school when his mom
surprised him with
his new debit card.
He had spent a
long time ⏰ saving
the money he earned
from shoveling and
mowing jobs and he
was finally ready
to spend it. He
was beyond excited
and immediately
wanted to buy some
treats from a
nearby grocery
store. His mom told
him they could go
together that
evening but Eli
couldn't contain
his excitement.
Eventually she
allowed him to make
the trip on his
own and being the
responsible little
boy he was. Eli
took his bike and
put on his helmet
before heading to
the store. Once he
had bought his
treats, he began
writing back home.
At the crossing, he
stopped and waited
for the light to
turn green. But he
had no idea that
he was never going
to...